

Daniel Zajkowski

E-mail: zajkowskidaniel@gmail.com Phone: +48 510 788 931 City: Katowice (Poland)

Github/LinkedIn

https://github.com/DanielZajkowski ?tab=repositories

https://www.linkedin.com/in/danielzajkowski-4168b6260/

Foreign Languages

- · English: advanced
- Japanese: conversational

Education

2011-10 - 2016-07

University of Silesia Education level: Engineer Field of study: Computer Science

Certificates

- · AWS Certified Machine Learning - Specialty
- · AWS Certified Data Analytics Specialty
- AWS Certified Developer Associate
- · IBM Certified Solution Architect Cloud 2016-01 2018-05 Pak for Data v4.x
- · IBM Certified Data Scientist Watson Specialist v1
- · Azure Fundamentals
- · Azure Al Fundamentals
- · Azure Data Fundamentals

About Me

I'm a Data & Al Delivery Consultant at IBM Technology Expert Labs. My previous expertise encompasses support for a cloud-based e-commerce platform with Apache services. Besides, I was supporting infrastructure level of Cloudera, workload management platform and cloud platform for application deployment and management.

Now, at IBM I specialize in delivering solution for AI technologies such as Watsonx and Cloud Pak for Data.

Work Experience

2022-09 - Now

Work at IBM

Position: Al Engineer - Delivery Consultant Responsibilities:

- · Providing technical expertise to IBM customers, including solution delivery, debugging, and support
- · Coding in Python
- · Prompt Engineering and Prompt Tuning of Large Language Models
- · Deploying AI models for customer environments
- · Programmatically leveraging the Watson NLP library for text analysis and extraction from documents
- · Developing various metrics for AI models evaluation
- Watsonx Assistant building dialogue flows, implementing LLM for chatbot responses, and configuring integration with communicators
- · Deploying code and integrating with Git repositories
- · Installing and managing software on Red Hat OpenShift

2021-03 - 2022-08

Work at Capgemini

Position: Big Data - Infrastructure Engineer

Responsibilities:

- Cloudera Hadoop maintaining infrastructure and various services for processing Big Data
- · IBM Spectrum LSF verifying workflows, performing diagnostics and software configuration
- Cloud Foundry troubleshooting platform and application issues for clients
- · Writing Bash scripts to automate tasks
- · Work on Red Hat Enterprise Linux operating system

2018-09 - 2021-03

Work at Capgemini

Position: Platform DevOps Support

Responsibilities:

- · Incident resolution problem investigation and solution provision
- · Support and implementation on SAP Hybris platform
- · Configuration and management of services for SAP Data Hub, Apache Tomcat and Apache Solr
- · Work with JIRA

Work at Onex Group

Position: Training developer

Responsibilities:

- · Online courses development of Microsoft products Windows, Office 365, SharePoint, and Power BI
- · Work with Adobe software Adobe Captivate and Adobe Premiere Pro

Key skills

- · Data Science, Machine Learning
- · Watsonx, Cloud Pak for Data
- · AWS, Azure, IBM Cloud, Red Hat Openshift
- · Python, Bash, Git